So, that was the last step!
وهكذا، كانت هذه الخطوة الأخيرة!
&gt;&gt; Woo hoo, congratulations!
&gt;&gt; مرحى، تهانينا!
You're done with the course!
لقد  انتهيتم من هذه الدورة!
&gt;&gt; For sure a great work.
&gt;&gt; إنه عمل رائع بالتأكيد.
&gt;&gt; Those were some really advanced concepts, and
&gt;&gt; كانت هذه بعض المفاهيم المتقدمة،
you got through all of them.
وقد تعلمتم كلًا منها.
&gt;&gt; Yeah, and quite a lot, I might add, in a short amount of time.
&gt;&gt; هذا صحيح، وأكثر من ذلك، وأود أن أضيف أنه تم ذلك في وقت قصير.
You learned how to make a network request to a web server
لقد تعلمتم كيفية القيام بطلب شبكة لخادم الويب
using a background thread and then you learned how to parse the JSON response.
باستخدام ترابط الخلفية ثم تعلمتم كيفية تحليل استجابة JSON
And then last and probably most important is you've learned to surface
ثم تعلمتم آخر شيء وربما الأكثر أهمية وهو إظهار
that data to the user in a pleasing way?
هذه البيانات للمستخدم بطريقة مُرضية.
&gt;&gt; We really hope that you'll continue building on what you've learned in this
&gt;&gt; نتمنى حقًا أنت تستمروا في استكمال ما تعلمتموه
course by creating other apps that connect to web APIs.
في هذه الدورة من خلال إنشاء تطبيقات أخرى تتصل بواجهات برمجة تطبيقات ويب.
&gt;&gt; All right that's a wrap.
&gt;&gt; حسنًا انتهى التصوير.
&gt;&gt; Wait, what?
&gt;&gt; أنتظر، ما هذا؟
&gt;&gt; Hey is someone going to let us out?
&gt;&gt; مهلًا، هل سيسمح لنا أحد بالذهاب؟
&gt;&gt; I'm hungry.
&gt;&gt; أنا جائع.
&gt;&gt; Me too.
&gt;&gt; وأنا أيضًا.